<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<window>
	<defaultcontrol always="true">61</defaultcontrol>
	<coordinates>
		<system>1</system>
		<posx>50</posx>
		<posy>50</posy>
	</coordinates>
	<animation effect="fade" time="250">WindowOpen</animation>
	<animation effect="fade" time="250">WindowClose</animation>
	<controls>
		<control type="image">
			<posx>0</posx>
			<posy>0</posy>
			<width>1180</width>
			<height>620</height>
			<texture border="40">DialogBack.png</texture>
		</control>
		<control type="image">
			<description>Dialog Header image</description>
			<posx>40</posx>
			<posy>16</posy>
			<width>1100</width>
			<height>40</height>
			<texture>dialogheader.png</texture>
		</control>
		<control type="label" id="1">
			<description>header label</description>
			<posx>40</posx>
			<posy>20</posy>
			<width>1100</width>
			<height>30</height>
			<font>font13_title</font>
			<label>IStream (Xunity) End User Agreement</label>
			<align>center</align>
			<aligny>center</aligny>
			<textcolor>FFEB9E17</textcolor>
			<shadowcolor>FF000000</shadowcolor>
		</control>
		<control type="button">
			<description>Close Window button</description>
			<posx>1090</posx>
			<posy>15</posy>
			<width>64</width>
			<height>32</height>
			<label>-</label>
			<font>-</font>
			<onclick>PreviousMenu</onclick>
			<texturefocus>DialogCloseButton-focus.png</texturefocus>
			<texturenofocus>DialogCloseButton.png</texturenofocus>
			<onleft>10</onleft>
			<onright>10</onright>
			<onup>10</onup>
			<ondown>10</ondown>
			<visible>system.getbool(input.enablemouse)</visible>
		</control>
		<control type="label" id="2">
			<description>terms header</description>
			<posx>30</posx>
			<posy>60</posy>
			<width>1115</width>
			<height>30</height>
			<align>left</align>
			<aligny>center</aligny>
			<label>[B]Important:[/B] Read carefully and accept the following Agreement. For more details, follow Mucky Duck @KODImediaportal on twitter</label>
			<font>font13</font>
		</control>		
		<control type="group">
			<visible>Control.IsVisible(11)</visible>
			<control type="image">
				<posx>30</posx>
				<posy>95</posy>
				<width>1115</width>
				<height>450</height>
				<texture border="40">black-back2.png</texture>
			</control>
			<control type="textbox" id="15">
				<description>terms details</description>
				<posx>35</posx>
				<posy>95</posy>
				<width>1097</width>
				<height>445</height>
				<label>[COLOR orange][B]Purpose and scope of Agreement[/B][/COLOR][CR]This IStream (Xunity) End User Agreement (“Agreement”) is a legal agreement between You, the end user (“You”) and Go Mad Marketing Limited (“Xunity”) governing Your use of:[CR]    (a) Any product that uses the Xunity Platform to play digital content distributed over the internet on a media device (“Media Device”);[CR]    (b) The firmware and software that Xunity installs on or updates directly to the Media Device (“the software”).[CR][CR]By using the Xunity Platform You are agreeing to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Agreement. If You do not agree to these terms and conditions, You are not granted any right to use the Xunity Platform, and You should stop using it right away. If You purchased Xunity hardware (Xunity Eclipse or other Xunity manufactured media devices), return it to the place where You obtained it for a refund.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]Nature of use[/B][/COLOR][CR]The Xunity Platform is intended for personal, non-commercial use only. You may not use it for any commercial or illegal purpose. Copying or re-distribution of the software or of any content delivered via the Media Device (“the Content”) are strictly prohibited. Except as expressly provided under this Agreement, You do not acquire any intellectual property or other proprietary rights in or to the Xunity Platform, the software or the content, including without limitation, any rights in patents, inventions, improvements, designs, trademarks, or copyrights nor do You acquire any rights in any confidential information or trade secrets. All rights not expressly granted to You in this Agreement are reserved by Go Mad Marketing Limited or its third party licensors. You may not remove or alter any trademark, logo, copyright or other proprietary notice in or on the Xunity Platform or the software.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]Software Licenses and Third Party Notices[/B][/COLOR][CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]Software License:[/B][/COLOR][CR]The software is proprietary to Go Mad Marketing Limited or its third party licensors and maybe used only in connection with the Xunity Platform. Subject to the terms of this Agreement, Go Mad Marketing Limited grants You a non-exclusive non-transferrable Licence to run the software and any updated versions provided to You by Go Mad Marketing Limited, only in and as incorporated in the Xunity Platform. This is a Licence and not a sale. You may not:[CR]   (a) Copy or distribute, sub-licence, lease, rent or otherwise transfer the software to any third party except as incorporated in the Xunity Platform;[CR]    (b) Modify, adapt, alter, translate or create derivative works of the software;[CR]    (c) Decompile, disassemble, reverse engineer or otherwise derive or attempt to derive source code from the software except as permitted by law; or[CR]    (d) Have any of the foregoing done for You by a third party.[CR][CR]Go Mad Marketing Limited reserves the right to update the software from time to time in its sole discretion, including adding, changing or removing functionalities and features, including but not limited to changing the user interface or the manner in which You are able to access content via the Xunity Platform.[CR][CR][B][COLOR gold]Permitted decompiling or copying:[/COLOR][/B][CR]Notwithstanding the restrictions in the software licence above or the third party notices below, nothing in this Agreement shall restrict You from;[CR]    (a) Decompiling the software, where it is necessary to decompile the software to obtain the information necessary to create an independent programme which can be operated with the software decompiled or with another programme and the information so obtained is not used for any purpose other than to obtain the information necessary to create an independent programme which can be operated with the software decompiled;[CR]    (b) The making of any back up copies of the software which is necessary for You to have for the purpose of the agreed use;[CR]    (c) The observing, studying or testing of the functioning of the software.[CR][CR][B][COLOR gold]Separately Licensed Code:[/COLOR][/B][CR]Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Agreement, certain components of the software, known as “free” or “open source” software code (the “Separately Licensed Code”) are subject to separate Licence terms and are not subject to the Licence granted above. As required by the terms of the relevant Separately Licensed Code Licences, Go Mad Marketing Limited make the Separately Licensed Code, and Go Mad Marketing Limited modifications to it, available on Go Mad Marketing Limited’s website at no charge.[CR][CR][B][COLOR gold]Third Party Notices:[/COLOR][/B][CR]Some of the technology utilised in the Xunity Platform is subject to Third Party Licences:[CR]    [B]+ Android OS:[/B] Apache Software License, Version 2.0 ("Apache 2.0"); For details, visit: [COLOR royalblue]http://source.android.com/[/COLOR][CR]    [B]+ XBMC Media Center:[/B] GPLv2 or later; For details, visit: [COLOR royalblue]http://xbmc.org/[/COLOR][CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]Use of Content:[/B][/COLOR][CR]For some of the content, You may be required to maintain a valid and active account in good standing with one or more content providers. You must adhere to Go Mad Marketing Limited’s terms of service and to the terms of service of any content provided whose content You choose to access. Go Mad Marketing Limited may add or remove content providers from time to time, in its sole discretion. Go Mad Marketing Limited reserves the right to remove from Your Xunity Platform Your access to certain content if Go Mad Marketing Limited has reason to believe that it is not properly authorised or Licensed, violates any law, or has been offered by a content provider in violation of any agreement between the content provider and Go Mad Marketing Limited. You are responsible for ensuring that any age restricted content is not viewed by any person not meeting the applicable age limits, as specified by law, regulation or the content provider. You agree to defend, indemnify and hold Go Mad Marketing Limited, its Directors, Officers, employees, Contractors, affiliates, suppliers and licensors (collectively “the Indemnified Parties”) harmless from any liability, damage, settlement, loss or expense (including, without limitation, legal fees, costs and outlay, incurred in connection with any third party Claim, demand, or action (“Claim”) brought or made against any of the Indemnified Parties arising out of or relating to any actions by You that infringe any copyright, trademark, trade secret, patent or other intellectual property right of any person or defame any person or violate their rights of publicity or privacy. If You have to indemnify any of the Indemnified Parties under this paragraph, Go Mad Marketing Limited and/or the relevant Indemnified Parties will have the right to control the defence, settlement and resolution of any Claim at Your sole expense. You may not settle or otherwise resolve any Claim without Go Mad Marketing Limited’s prior express written permission.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]IStream[/B][/COLOR][CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]What is IStream?[/B][/COLOR][CR]IStream acts as a bookmarker for all your favorite websites that contain streaming content. It organises all your favorite websites when they have been converted into extensions and hold them in a data management folder. You then select the extension associated with a particular website and all the content is then viewable on your tv screen.[CR][CR]IStream relies on extensions in order to provide the content. By itself, iStream only provides a shell that performs basic user and content related functions as requested by the extension like:[CR] + Play a file or stream [CR] + Add item to favorites [CR] + Subscribe to an item [CR] + Track watched status [CR] + Perform search requests [CR] + etc. [CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]What is an IStream Extension?[/B][/COLOR][CR]IStream relies on extensions in order to function. An extension is a website that has been converted to iStream code in order to function with our software. As soon as the extension has been selected it will function in the same way the website would function but making it work with iStream makes it easier to access and play the content[CR][CR][B][COLOR gold]IStream and Extensions License:[/COLOR][/B][CR]IStream has been created by the Go Mad Marketing Limited "Xunity" team and is the sole owner of the software. IStream Extensions are owned by the person or entity responsible for creating the extension.[CR][CR][CR][B][COLOR orange]DISCLAIMER[/COLOR][/B][CR]IStream (Xunity) facilitates, using various search engines and open-source code repositories, the searching by users for third party iStream extensions.  IStream (Xunity) has no knowledge of, and cannot verify the security or legality of such third party extensions, and it is entirely a matter for the user to satisfy himself or herself regarding the safety or legality of such extensions, or the terms and conditions (including charging for content) which may be imposed by the owner of the content on such extensions.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]Privacy[/B][/COLOR][CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]Xunity Platform:[/B][/COLOR][CR]This statement relates to our privacy practices in relation to the Xunity Platform. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites. Any external links to any other websites are clearly identifiable as such. Some technical terms used in this statement are explained at the end of this page.[CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]General Statement:[/B][/COLOR][CR]Go Mad Marketing Limited fully respects Your right to privacy, and will not collect any personal information about You via the Xunity Platform without Your clear permission. Any personal information which You volunteer to Go Mad Marketing Limited will be treated with the highest standards of security and confidentiality, strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1988 and 2003.[CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]Collection and Use of Personal Information:[/B][/COLOR][CR]Go Mad Marketing Limited does not collect any personal data about You via the Xunity Platform, apart from information which You volunteer. Any information which You provide in this way is not made available to any third parties, and is used by Go Mad Marketing Limited only in line with the purposes for which You provided it. Your personal data may also be a annonymised and used for statistical purposes.[CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]Request Regarding Data Supplied Via the Xunity Platform:[/B][/COLOR][CR]On request, we supply copies of Your personal data which You may have supplied via the Xunity Platform. If You wish to obtain such copies You must email Go Mad Marketing Limited at [COLOR royalblue]support@xunity.tv[/COLOR]. You should include any personal identifiers which You supplied earlier. Your request will be dealt with as soon as possible and will not take more than 40 days to process.[CR][CR]If You discover that Go Mad Marketing Limited hold inaccurate information about You, You can request Go Mad Marketing Limited to correct that information. Such a request must be via email.[CR][CR]In certain circumstances You may also request that data which You have supplied via the Xunity Platform be deleted. If You wish to request a deletion, You would generally be expected to identify some contravention of data protection law in the manner in which Go Mad Marketing Limited processes the data concerned.[CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]Complaints About Data Processed via the Xunity Platform:[/B][/COLOR][CR]If You are concerned about how personal data is processed via the Xunity Platform, please do not hesitate to bring such concerns to the attention of Go Mad Marketing Limited at the email address above.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]Advertising and Promotional Messages[/B][/COLOR][CR]Go Mad Marketing Limited and the content providers have reserved the rights to deliver and display advertising and promotional messages to You via the Xunity Platform and to include such advertising and promotional messages in or with any user interface, notices or content that are displayed via the Xunity Platform.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]Warranty[/B][/COLOR][CR][I][COLOR gold]In this section, Xunity Platform refers only to Xunity hardware platform i.e. Xunity Eclipse or other Xunity manufactured media devices.[/COLOR][/I][CR]Subject to the additional terms and conditions set forth below, this warranty is provided only to the person or entity that originally purchased the Xunity Platform one of Go Mad Marketing Limited’s authorised retailers or distributors, and only for Xunity Platforms purchased and delivered to the End User within the United Kingdom and Republic of Ireland.[CR][CR]For Warranty on purchases made outside of the United Kingdom and Republic of Ireland, directly contact the person, place or entity (distributor, retailer, or reseller) from whom or where you made the purchase.[CR][CR]Go Mad Marketing Limited warrants the Xunity Platform hardware against defects in materials and workmanship under normal use for a period of 12 months from the date of the purchase (“the Warranty Period”). If Go Mad Marketing Limited determines that a Xunity Platform’s hardware is defective, Go Mad Marketing Limited will either repair the unit or replace the unit with either a new or rebuilt Xunity Platform, at its option. If the Warranty Period has expired or is otherwise not applicable (see Scope and Limitation on Warranty below) we will return the Xunity Platform to You.[CR][CR]The Warranty on an Xunity Platform is limited to the repair or replacement of defective units as described in the limited Warranty section above. This Warranty does not cover customer training or education, installation, set up adjustments, or signal reception problems. This Warranty also does not cover any issue related to the service provided by Your internet service provider or content providers, including but not limited to service disruption, changes in service terms, changes in offerings, changes in format, or technical problems. This Warranty does not cover damage due to acts of God, accident, misuse, abuse, negligence, commercial use or modification of, or to any part of the Xunity Platform. This Warranty does not cover damage due to improper operation or maintenance, connection to improper voltage supply or attempted repair by anyone other than a facility authorised by Go Mad Marketing Limited to service Your Xunity Platform. This Warranty does not cover consumables (such as fuses and batteries) or the AC power adaptor.[CR][CR]THIS LIMITED WARRANTY DOES NOT AFFECT YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS, INCLUDING RIGHTS AGAINST GO MAD MARKETING LIMITED’S AUTHORISED RETAILERS OR DISTRIBUTORS. IF YOU REQUIRE MORE INFORMATION ON YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS, YOU SHOULD CONTACT THE NATIONAL CONSUMER AGENCY OR CITIZEN’S ADVICE BUREAU.[CR][CR]In no event will either party or Go Mad Marketing Limited’s suppliers be liable for any consequential, special, exemplary, incidental and indirect damages, or for loss of revenue or profits or data or use or for the cost of substitute goods, whether in Contract or Tort (including negligence) arising out of, or in connection with an Xunity Platform, the software, the separately licensed code, or Your use thereof. Nothing in this Agreement will exclude or limit either parties liability (i) for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation; (ii) for death or personal injury caused by its negligence; (iii) under the Indemnity herein; or (iv) for any other liability which cannot be excluded by law.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]Consent To Use of Data[/B][/COLOR][CR]You agree that Go Mad Marketing Limited or a third party contracted by Go Mad Marketing Limited may collect and use technical usage data and related information, including but not limited to information about your device, system and software and peripherals that has gathered periodically to facilitate the provision of updates, product support and other services (if any) to You. Go Mad Marketing Limited may use this information, as long as it is in a form that does not personally identify you, to improve its products or to provide services or technologies to You. This data will be handled in accordance with the Privacy Statement set out above.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]Miscellaneous[/B][/COLOR][CR]This Agreement is the final, complete and exclusive Agreement between You and Go Mad Marketing Limited relating to an Xunity Platform and the software and supercedes all prior or contemporaneous proposals, advertisements, representations, understandings, or agreements relating thereto, whether oral or written. No waiver or modification of the Agreement will be valid unless signed by both Go Mad Marketing Limited and You. Your right to use the software and/or the Xunity Platform will immediately terminate upon your breach of any applicable provision of this Agreement. The waiver of a breach of any term hereof will in no way be construed as a waiver of any other term or breach hereof. If any provision of this Agreement is held by a Court of competent jurisdiction to be unenforceable, the remaining provisions of this Agreement will remain in full force and effect. The construction, validity and performance of this Agreement and all non-contractual obligations arising from or connected with this Agreement, the Privacy Policy and any Go Mad Marketing Limited website policy shall be governed by the laws of Ireland. Any action or proceeding brought to adjudicate any dispute related to this Agreement, the Privacy Policy or any Go Mad Marketing Limited website policies shall be subject to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the Irish Courts, except as otherwise agreed by the parties in writing. The United Nations convention on contracts for the international sale of goods shall not apply to this Agreement.[CR]</label>
				<font>font12</font>
				<align>justify</align>
				<textcolor>white</textcolor>
				<shadowcolor>black</shadowcolor>
				<pagecontrol>61</pagecontrol>
			</control>
			<control type="scrollbar" id="61">
				<posx>1130</posx>
				<posy>90</posy>
				<width>25</width>
				<height>462</height>
				<texturesliderbackground border="0,14,0,14">ScrollBarV.png</texturesliderbackground>
				<texturesliderbar border="0,14,0,14">ScrollBarV_bar.png</texturesliderbar>
				<texturesliderbarfocus border="0,14,0,14">ScrollBarV_bar_focus.png</texturesliderbarfocus>
				<textureslidernib>ScrollBarNib.png</textureslidernib>
				<textureslidernibfocus>ScrollBarNib.png</textureslidernibfocus>
				<onleft>61</onleft>
				<onright>61</onright>
				<ondown>11</ondown>
				<onup>61</onup>
				<showonepage>true</showonepage>
				<orientation>vertical</orientation>
			</control>
		</control>
		<control type="group">
			<visible>Control.IsVisible(13)</visible>
			<control type="image">
				<posx>30</posx>
				<posy>95</posy>
				<width>1115</width>
				<height>450</height>
				<texture border="40">black-back2.png</texture>
			</control>
			<control type="textbox" id="15">
				<description>terms details</description>
				<posx>35</posx>
				<posy>95</posy>
				<width>1097</width>
				<height>445</height>
				<label>[COLOR orange][B]Purpose and scope of Agreement[/B][/COLOR][CR]This IStream (Xunity) End User Agreement (“Agreement”) is a legal agreement between You, the end user (“You”) and Go Mad Marketing Limited (“Xunity”) governing Your use of:[CR]    (a) Any product that uses the Xunity Platform to play digital content distributed over the internet on a media device (“Media Device”);[CR]    (b) The firmware and software that Xunity installs on or updates directly to the Media Device (“the software”).[CR][CR]By using the Xunity Platform You are agreeing to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Agreement. If You do not agree to these terms and conditions, You are not granted any right to use the Xunity Platform, and You should stop using it right away. If You purchased Xunity hardware (Xunity Eclipse or other Xunity manufactured media devices), return it to the place where You obtained it for a refund.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]Nature of use[/B][/COLOR][CR]The Xunity Platform is intended for personal, non-commercial use only. You may not use it for any commercial or illegal purpose. Copying or re-distribution of the software or of any content delivered via the Media Device (“the Content”) are strictly prohibited. Except as expressly provided under this Agreement, You do not acquire any intellectual property or other proprietary rights in or to the Xunity Platform, the software or the content, including without limitation, any rights in patents, inventions, improvements, designs, trademarks, or copyrights nor do You acquire any rights in any confidential information or trade secrets. All rights not expressly granted to You in this Agreement are reserved by Go Mad Marketing Limited or its third party licensors. You may not remove or alter any trademark, logo, copyright or other proprietary notice in or on the Xunity Platform or the software.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]Software Licenses and Third Party Notices[/B][/COLOR][CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]Software License:[/B][/COLOR][CR]The software is proprietary to Go Mad Marketing Limited or its third party licensors and maybe used only in connection with the Xunity Platform. Subject to the terms of this Agreement, Go Mad Marketing Limited grants You a non-exclusive non-transferrable Licence to run the software and any updated versions provided to You by Go Mad Marketing Limited, only in and as incorporated in the Xunity Platform. This is a Licence and not a sale. You may not:[CR]   (a) Copy or distribute, sub-licence, lease, rent or otherwise transfer the software to any third party except as incorporated in the Xunity Platform;[CR]    (b) Modify, adapt, alter, translate or create derivative works of the software;[CR]    (c) Decompile, disassemble, reverse engineer or otherwise derive or attempt to derive source code from the software except as permitted by law; or[CR]    (d) Have any of the foregoing done for You by a third party.[CR][CR]Go Mad Marketing Limited reserves the right to update the software from time to time in its sole discretion, including adding, changing or removing functionalities and features, including but not limited to changing the user interface or the manner in which You are able to access content via the Xunity Platform.[CR][CR][B][COLOR gold]Permitted decompiling or copying:[/COLOR][/B][CR]Notwithstanding the restrictions in the software licence above or the third party notices below, nothing in this Agreement shall restrict You from;[CR]    (a) Decompiling the software, where it is necessary to decompile the software to obtain the information necessary to create an independent programme which can be operated with the software decompiled or with another programme and the information so obtained is not used for any purpose other than to obtain the information necessary to create an independent programme which can be operated with the software decompiled;[CR]    (b) The making of any back up copies of the software which is necessary for You to have for the purpose of the agreed use;[CR]    (c) The observing, studying or testing of the functioning of the software.[CR][CR][B][COLOR gold]Separately Licensed Code:[/COLOR][/B][CR]Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Agreement, certain components of the software, known as “free” or “open source” software code (the “Separately Licensed Code”) are subject to separate Licence terms and are not subject to the Licence granted above. As required by the terms of the relevant Separately Licensed Code Licences, Go Mad Marketing Limited make the Separately Licensed Code, and Go Mad Marketing Limited modifications to it, available on Go Mad Marketing Limited’s website at no charge.[CR][CR][B][COLOR gold]Third Party Notices:[/COLOR][/B][CR]Some of the technology utilised in the Xunity Platform is subject to Third Party Licences:[CR]    [B]+ Android OS:[/B] Apache Software License, Version 2.0 ("Apache 2.0"); For details, visit: [COLOR royalblue]http://source.android.com/[/COLOR][CR]    [B]+ XBMC Media Center:[/B] GPLv2 or later; For details, visit: [COLOR royalblue]http://xbmc.org/[/COLOR][CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]Use of Content:[/B][/COLOR][CR]For some of the content, You may be required to maintain a valid and active account in good standing with one or more content providers. You must adhere to Go Mad Marketing Limited’s terms of service and to the terms of service of any content provided whose content You choose to access. Go Mad Marketing Limited may add or remove content providers from time to time, in its sole discretion. Go Mad Marketing Limited reserves the right to remove from Your Xunity Platform Your access to certain content if Go Mad Marketing Limited has reason to believe that it is not properly authorised or Licensed, violates any law, or has been offered by a content provider in violation of any agreement between the content provider and Go Mad Marketing Limited. You are responsible for ensuring that any age restricted content is not viewed by any person not meeting the applicable age limits, as specified by law, regulation or the content provider. You agree to defend, indemnify and hold Go Mad Marketing Limited, its Directors, Officers, employees, Contractors, affiliates, suppliers and licensors (collectively “the Indemnified Parties”) harmless from any liability, damage, settlement, loss or expense (including, without limitation, legal fees, costs and outlay, incurred in connection with any third party Claim, demand, or action (“Claim”) brought or made against any of the Indemnified Parties arising out of or relating to any actions by You that infringe any copyright, trademark, trade secret, patent or other intellectual property right of any person or defame any person or violate their rights of publicity or privacy. If You have to indemnify any of the Indemnified Parties under this paragraph, Go Mad Marketing Limited and/or the relevant Indemnified Parties will have the right to control the defence, settlement and resolution of any Claim at Your sole expense. You may not settle or otherwise resolve any Claim without Go Mad Marketing Limited’s prior express written permission.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]IStream[/B][/COLOR][CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]What is IStream?[/B][/COLOR][CR]IStream acts as a bookmarker for all your favorite websites that contain streaming content. It organises all your favorite websites when they have been converted into extensions and hold them in a data management folder. You then select the extension associated with a particular website and all the content is then viewable on your tv screen.[CR][CR]IStream relies on extensions in order to provide the content. By itself, iStream only provides a shell that performs basic user and content related functions as requested by the extension like:[CR] + Play a file or stream [CR] + Add item to favorites [CR] + Subscribe to an item [CR] + Track watched status [CR] + Perform search requests [CR] + etc. [CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]What is an IStream Extension?[/B][/COLOR][CR]IStream relies on extensions in order to function. An extension is a website that has been converted to iStream code in order to function with our software. As soon as the extension has been selected it will function in the same way the website would function but making it work with iStream makes it easier to access and play the content[CR][CR][B][COLOR gold]IStream and Extensions License:[/COLOR][/B][CR]IStream has been created by the Go Mad Marketing Limited "Xunity" team and is the sole owner of the software. IStream Extensions are owned by the person or entity responsible for creating the extension.[CR][CR][CR][B][COLOR orange]DISCLAIMER[/COLOR][/B][CR]IStream (Xunity) facilitates, using various search engines and open-source code repositories, the searching by users for third party iStream extensions.  IStream (Xunity) has no knowledge of, and cannot verify the security or legality of such third party extensions, and it is entirely a matter for the user to satisfy himself or herself regarding the safety or legality of such extensions, or the terms and conditions (including charging for content) which may be imposed by the owner of the content on such extensions.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]Privacy[/B][/COLOR][CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]Xunity Platform:[/B][/COLOR][CR]This statement relates to our privacy practices in relation to the Xunity Platform. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites. Any external links to any other websites are clearly identifiable as such. Some technical terms used in this statement are explained at the end of this page.[CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]General Statement:[/B][/COLOR][CR]Go Mad Marketing Limited fully respects Your right to privacy, and will not collect any personal information about You via the Xunity Platform without Your clear permission. Any personal information which You volunteer to Go Mad Marketing Limited will be treated with the highest standards of security and confidentiality, strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1988 and 2003.[CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]Collection and Use of Personal Information:[/B][/COLOR][CR]Go Mad Marketing Limited does not collect any personal data about You via the Xunity Platform, apart from information which You volunteer. Any information which You provide in this way is not made available to any third parties, and is used by Go Mad Marketing Limited only in line with the purposes for which You provided it. Your personal data may also be a annonymised and used for statistical purposes.[CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]Request Regarding Data Supplied Via the Xunity Platform:[/B][/COLOR][CR]On request, we supply copies of Your personal data which You may have supplied via the Xunity Platform. If You wish to obtain such copies You must email Go Mad Marketing Limited at [COLOR royalblue]support@xunity.tv[/COLOR]. You should include any personal identifiers which You supplied earlier. Your request will be dealt with as soon as possible and will not take more than 40 days to process.[CR][CR]If You discover that Go Mad Marketing Limited hold inaccurate information about You, You can request Go Mad Marketing Limited to correct that information. Such a request must be via email.[CR][CR]In certain circumstances You may also request that data which You have supplied via the Xunity Platform be deleted. If You wish to request a deletion, You would generally be expected to identify some contravention of data protection law in the manner in which Go Mad Marketing Limited processes the data concerned.[CR][CR][COLOR gold][B]Complaints About Data Processed via the Xunity Platform:[/B][/COLOR][CR]If You are concerned about how personal data is processed via the Xunity Platform, please do not hesitate to bring such concerns to the attention of Go Mad Marketing Limited at the email address above.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]Advertising and Promotional Messages[/B][/COLOR][CR]Go Mad Marketing Limited and the content providers have reserved the rights to deliver and display advertising and promotional messages to You via the Xunity Platform and to include such advertising and promotional messages in or with any user interface, notices or content that are displayed via the Xunity Platform.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]Warranty[/B][/COLOR][CR][I][COLOR gold]In this section, Xunity Platform refers only to Xunity hardware platform i.e. Xunity Eclipse or other Xunity manufactured media devices.[/COLOR][/I][CR]Subject to the additional terms and conditions set forth below, this warranty is provided only to the person or entity that originally purchased the Xunity Platform one of Go Mad Marketing Limited’s authorised retailers or distributors, and only for Xunity Platforms purchased and delivered to the End User within the United Kingdom and Republic of Ireland.[CR][CR]For Warranty on purchases made outside of the United Kingdom and Republic of Ireland, directly contact the person, place or entity (distributor, retailer, or reseller) from whom or where you made the purchase.[CR][CR]Go Mad Marketing Limited warrants the Xunity Platform hardware against defects in materials and workmanship under normal use for a period of 12 months from the date of the purchase (“the Warranty Period”). If Go Mad Marketing Limited determines that a Xunity Platform’s hardware is defective, Go Mad Marketing Limited will either repair the unit or replace the unit with either a new or rebuilt Xunity Platform, at its option. If the Warranty Period has expired or is otherwise not applicable (see Scope and Limitation on Warranty below) we will return the Xunity Platform to You.[CR][CR]The Warranty on an Xunity Platform is limited to the repair or replacement of defective units as described in the limited Warranty section above. This Warranty does not cover customer training or education, installation, set up adjustments, or signal reception problems. This Warranty also does not cover any issue related to the service provided by Your internet service provider or content providers, including but not limited to service disruption, changes in service terms, changes in offerings, changes in format, or technical problems. This Warranty does not cover damage due to acts of God, accident, misuse, abuse, negligence, commercial use or modification of, or to any part of the Xunity Platform. This Warranty does not cover damage due to improper operation or maintenance, connection to improper voltage supply or attempted repair by anyone other than a facility authorised by Go Mad Marketing Limited to service Your Xunity Platform. This Warranty does not cover consumables (such as fuses and batteries) or the AC power adaptor.[CR][CR]THIS LIMITED WARRANTY DOES NOT AFFECT YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS, INCLUDING RIGHTS AGAINST GO MAD MARKETING LIMITED’S AUTHORISED RETAILERS OR DISTRIBUTORS. IF YOU REQUIRE MORE INFORMATION ON YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS, YOU SHOULD CONTACT THE NATIONAL CONSUMER AGENCY OR CITIZEN’S ADVICE BUREAU.[CR][CR]In no event will either party or Go Mad Marketing Limited’s suppliers be liable for any consequential, special, exemplary, incidental and indirect damages, or for loss of revenue or profits or data or use or for the cost of substitute goods, whether in Contract or Tort (including negligence) arising out of, or in connection with an Xunity Platform, the software, the separately licensed code, or Your use thereof. Nothing in this Agreement will exclude or limit either parties liability (i) for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation; (ii) for death or personal injury caused by its negligence; (iii) under the Indemnity herein; or (iv) for any other liability which cannot be excluded by law.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]Consent To Use of Data[/B][/COLOR][CR]You agree that Go Mad Marketing Limited or a third party contracted by Go Mad Marketing Limited may collect and use technical usage data and related information, including but not limited to information about your device, system and software and peripherals that has gathered periodically to facilitate the provision of updates, product support and other services (if any) to You. Go Mad Marketing Limited may use this information, as long as it is in a form that does not personally identify you, to improve its products or to provide services or technologies to You. This data will be handled in accordance with the Privacy Statement set out above.[CR][CR][CR][COLOR orange][B]Miscellaneous[/B][/COLOR][CR]This Agreement is the final, complete and exclusive Agreement between You and Go Mad Marketing Limited relating to an Xunity Platform and the software and supercedes all prior or contemporaneous proposals, advertisements, representations, understandings, or agreements relating thereto, whether oral or written. No waiver or modification of the Agreement will be valid unless signed by both Go Mad Marketing Limited and You. Your right to use the software and/or the Xunity Platform will immediately terminate upon your breach of any applicable provision of this Agreement. The waiver of a breach of any term hereof will in no way be construed as a waiver of any other term or breach hereof. If any provision of this Agreement is held by a Court of competent jurisdiction to be unenforceable, the remaining provisions of this Agreement will remain in full force and effect. The construction, validity and performance of this Agreement and all non-contractual obligations arising from or connected with this Agreement, the Privacy Policy and any Go Mad Marketing Limited website policy shall be governed by the laws of Ireland. Any action or proceeding brought to adjudicate any dispute related to this Agreement, the Privacy Policy or any Go Mad Marketing Limited website policies shall be subject to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the Irish Courts, except as otherwise agreed by the parties in writing. The United Nations convention on contracts for the international sale of goods shall not apply to this Agreement.[CR]</label>
				<font>font12</font>
				<align>justify</align>
				<textcolor>white</textcolor>
				<shadowcolor>black</shadowcolor>
				<pagecontrol>62</pagecontrol>
			</control>
			<control type="scrollbar" id="62">
				<visible>Control.IsVisible(13)</visible>
				<posx>1130</posx>
				<posy>90</posy>
				<width>25</width>
				<height>462</height>
				<texturesliderbackground border="0,14,0,14">ScrollBarV.png</texturesliderbackground>
				<texturesliderbar border="0,14,0,14">ScrollBarV_bar.png</texturesliderbar>
				<texturesliderbarfocus border="0,14,0,14">ScrollBarV_bar_focus.png</texturesliderbarfocus>
				<textureslidernib>ScrollBarNib.png</textureslidernib>
				<textureslidernibfocus>ScrollBarNib.png</textureslidernibfocus>
				<onleft>62</onleft>
				<onright>62</onright>
				<ondown>13</ondown>
				<onup>62</onup>
				<showonepage>true</showonepage>
				<orientation>vertical</orientation>
			</control>
		</control>
		<control type="button" id="10">
			<description>Decline button</description>
			<posx>375</posx>
			<posy>555</posy>
			<width>200</width>
			<height>40</height>
			<label>Decline</label>
			<font>font12_title</font>
			<textcolor>white</textcolor>
			<focusedcolor>white</focusedcolor>
			<align>center</align>
			<onleft>11</onleft>
			<onright>11</onright>
			<onup>61</onup>
			<ondown>10</ondown>
		</control>
		<control type="button" id="13">
			<description>OK Button</description>
			<posx>500</posx>
			<posy>555</posy>
			<width>200</width>
			<height>40</height>
			<label>OK</label>
			<font>font12_title</font>
			<textcolor>white</textcolor>
			<focusedcolor>white</focusedcolor>
			<align>center</align>
			<onleft>13</onleft>
			<onright>13</onright>
			<onup>62</onup>
			<ondown>13</ondown>
		</control>
		<control type="button" id="11">
			<description>Accept button</description>
			<posx>605</posx>
			<posy>555</posy>
			<width>200</width>
			<height>40</height>
			<label>Accept</label>
			<font>font12_title</font>
			<textcolor>white</textcolor>
			<focusedcolor>white</focusedcolor>
			<align>center</align>
			<onleft>10</onleft>
			<onright>10</onright>
			<onup>61</onup>
			<ondown>11</ondown>
		</control>
	</controls>
</window>